[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Who is the better cricketer?",
    "options": ["Rohit", "Virat"],
    "answer": "Virat"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Which is your preferred operating system?",
    "options": ["Windows", "Linux"],
    "answer": "Linux"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which game do you prefer?",
    "options": ["Chess", "Ludo"],
    "answer": "Chess"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Who is the better T20 opening batsman?",
    "options": ["KL Rahul", "Sanju Samson"],
    "answer": "KL Rahul"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Which is the better sport?",
    "options": ["Cricket", "Badminton"],
    "answer": "Cricket"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What would you like to call money?",
    "options": ["Bucks", "Rupees"],
    "answer": "Rupees"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which is the better web series?",
    "options": ["Breaking Bad", "Squid Game"],
    "answer": "Breaking Bad"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Who is the better batsman?",
    "options": ["Kedar Jadhav", "Babar Azam" ],
    "answer": "Kedar Jadhav"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Who is the better bowler?",
    "options": ["Shaheen Shah Afridi", "Shardul Thakur"],
    "answer": "Shardul Thakur"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What is your favorite chocolate?",
    "options": ["Munch","Dairy Milk"],
    "answer": "Munch"
  }
]
